[Music]
hello and welcome to our busy Center
lunch event about um our new 2024
release wave
1 today will present you what is new
related with automated IRS 1089
reporting this is amazing topic but keep
in mind this is local topic only for the
United States
Market uh let's first introduce ourself
uh together with me today I have Arthur
Vel software engineer who made the
biggest part of this functionality and
on my side my name is Alexander toic I'm
product manager responsible for this
feature
so let's first explain shortly what we
talk today I will first make some short
introduction and it will be mostly
related what did we have earlier why we
decided to move uh to new app to make
design then we will explain you New
Concept of this app uh not only concept
but all new values we'll get uh with
this redesign because this is not only
technical redesign we are bringing new
values
there shortly briefly explain U main
features an overview why briefly because
ar2 will show full demo end to end
scenario with all these details so you
will see in a practice how it works so
let's start with the
introduction um let's remind us what
form 1089 is if you didn't work earlier
with that I hope you are but if not form
1089 is one of several IRS text forms
used as a mention only United States uh
1089 form is recorded entity or person
other than your employee uh gave or paid
you a
money that means that payer must fill
1089 form and send copy to the receiver
in our case it be sented to vendor and
the other side to IRS so pair can file
in two ways um pair can print and mail
paper forms that means printing on
original uh preprinted uh IRS forms and
and send this to IRS and send the same
copy to the vendor and other option is
electronically through
IIs or information return intake system
that means fully
automatically um printing on prep
printed forms and mailing uh to IRS and
vendors this is something what we had
earlier let's say we still have this
inside the BS Centra but this is old
feature and now with new app you can use
this fully integrated ation together
with electronically sending through IRS
ir and um emailing to your
customers
now uh when we talk
about what we had let's remind you we
had 1089 setup in 1089 setup we had some
codes and rules uh only for the current
year so you could you couldn't have um
active boat years for example now uh
2024 and uh previous 2024 or the next
one so you could have only one a year
and U updated wait for Microsoft so
there is process cons it was not so
complicated to uh to have all these
details you had to wait Microsoft and
this is good and bad you had to wait
because uh you had to wait Microsoft
finish with with everything and then to
refresh and what after refresh after
refresh once updated there is no way
back so you had to report earlier you
had to finish with the last year and
then you need to refresh with the new
data and you can continue to work with
new
data and yeah this is I said all the
time good and bad what we had more we
had a really easy window setup it was a
really easy straightforward uh you you
had to open vendor to set up this vendor
1089 liable you had to uh choose 1089
code default code for this vendor and
yes Defender should be nature person and
you had option to have only one 1089
code per vendor you could change this on
document but in general only 1089 per
Vendor by default process
was let's say easy but sometimes it
could be
complicated uh you had to post purchase
invoice and then you had payment you had
to register payment and that's it but
what could what could happen you didn't
configure properly vendor so you didn't
have proper IRS code there so in this
case you could eventually go to vendor
Ledger entries if you know for this
situation so you couldn't just update on
vendor no you had to update on vendor
site but you need to go to vendor Ledger
entries to find all these entries and
manually to change vendor
entries yes it was possible but
definitely not the best process you
could imagine but yeah we had it and
when we finish with everything so you
could register all these details you had
to print forms print reports uh stand
reports and the forms so again just to
remind you had to use standard 10 IRS
forms and this is where all headaches
are
starting yes you had print you had to
print it was let's say straight for a
process not such a big problem
but as again just remind you original
forms not PDFs we could uh download from
ours side oursite only original forms so
this is um maybe easy on the first site
but when Microsoft had to adjust these
phones for printing every year we could
expect one field here and there changing
sometime some things and Microsoft
couldn't start um updating report layout
before we get original first we had to
get all changes then we had to get
original form to order from IRS original
form so we could test printing original
forms then in depend from printer to
printer and all the time we had issues
something like that just missed you know
all these boxes with address with the uh
x with numbers and sometimes this is a
problem about uh report layout design
sometimes this is a problem how you
configure your printer and all the time
it had a problem this is just one of
examples all youc uh 2021 year this is
just all example but this is how things
were going and it was the most annoying
especially it was in a tough period you
had to report not too late not to pay
fees so
so this is uh something what we wanted
to change and what we did with the New
Concept we wanted to create to redesign
and um not only to R redesign because we
wanted when we looked in BC ideas I
think that uh five six different ideas
about different types of redesign was
already required from um our partners
maybe customers as well I don't know all
these old names so it was required from
your side and and now we decided to
redesign but every time when we want to
redesign this is not just making all
these features in a different way as a
app we wanted to bring some new value to
to you and now let's see first
completely process flow how it will
break in the future first we are
starting with setting up what you need
to do you need to set up your vendors it
will be a little bit different we want
to give you little bit more space what
you can configure there you will see
later uh in AR demos then G yeah you
need to post documents and you need to
register payments so this is the same
thing this is uh something we are
enforced by the law but after setting up
we need to calculate so we are starting
to work we have already documents uh end
of year so end of year we need to
calculate everything we need to run 10
10 calculation but now how we calculate
we are taking information from setup now
we still have setup 1089 actually this
is uh IRS setup but what we have there
um now we have IRS setup with different
periods so you can have different setups
for one year another year next year so
you do not need to update and uh if you
forget to calculate something from
previous year you are in trouble no you
can have all this uh reporting
information in a parallel you just need
to to choose what is active here for you
then we have there 1089 forms form boxes
and everything so when you R calculation
we assume we you have all documents and
payment register now we have uh all all
this uh setup information about 1089
reports and system will just calculate
it and then you calculate what you will
get now first value you will get not
first this is now second value because
after setup you will get 1089 for
documents now we have documents with
header and
lines uh you will see a little bit more
why this is important why this is
benefit uh first when we go to the next
stage to review you can much easier
review earlier you could you could
calculate and you could report what you
calculated it was really complicated to
to check if everything was okay if you
miss some documents or from some reason
you need to adjust some information now
we have this form we have actually this
document so you can check all details
and if everything is okay we can handle
with different statuses and more
important after reporting we will have
1089 forms in a history so you can check
history from previous year previous
years and of course you can conf your
retention policy if you have thousands
of forms and you are taking care about
your database space yeah you can you can
configure retention policy and you can
remove old I don't know for example more
than three years old forms whatever you
decide now we have next stage to
schedule and your schedule you can
schedule if file any delivering what is
important how it work now we are
reporting directly to through e file
through
IIs uh platform so we are reporting
there uh it will be configure you just
need to have your credentials there and
system will send automatically
electronically why this is important I
didn't mention previously you could
print now you cannot use pre-printed
forms but this is important because even
now uh you could print only if you have
up to 10 uh reports per year so this is
a really small number if you have if you
had more you had to report through
platform so earlier you you had to
prepare file and to report manually now
we automated fully it will be
automatically when you decide to report
it will be reported to IRS then we have
second part we need to print uh forms
and to send to our vendors so how it it
work we will print not on preprinted
forms we will use uh PL paper uh we'll
create 1099 PDF copy
substitutions what it means you will
have all the details you have on a
regular 1089 but it is the copy
substitution because law uh enable us to
use this copy substitution we just need
to have all details we we have in our
standard printed forms and we can use
this um copy substitutions if you are
report directly to IRS through their
apis and now what is even more important
for these copy substitutions you are in
control of that you can see on the left
side 1089 layout setup
um actually this is not the right name
for this setup I just wanted to make it
as simpler here on um uh this chart you
can you will get by Microsoft already
configure reports but if there is some
changes and you cannot wait to Microsoft
Microsoft finish and update the new in X
minor all these details you can easily
add just new box put description what is
in this box uh say okay in this box I
will collect uh this value from this
place so this is now much much easier
for you and it will be much easier for
Microsoft Microsoft can provide much
much faster support and
um not having all these issues in
Communications uh preparing layout this
is every time it come to layout 1 mm
left and right up and down this is
really complicated now it will be much
much straightforward so this is not
complex uh topic and now okay we have
PDFs what we'll do with the PDFs we are
enabling on vendors if vendor accept
consent to receive these
documents electronically we can fully
automate once when you report you can
put in a background process and send all
emails if you have thousands of uh
vendors you will send automatically
thousands of emails to them and that's
it you reported but if some of your
vendors do not want to uh give you
content you still have printing for
manually delivering so you can again you
can start a process to print all these
uh forms on a plain paper and then you
can use standard mailing process for
execution uh I want to emphasize one
thing here because this is uh something
what we will um do in this major but
some things will come in next few minors
and what it means this black box uh
connection with uh IRS through Iris uh
portal will come in next few minors uh
now I cannot promise exactly uh date
because we are waiting some confirmation
from IRS as soon as we get we will
finish this part but what I can say it
will be before your reporting period
because now we have more than enough
time to have everything ready for end of
year but idea is not to deliver this on
the end of here we want to deliver this
as soon as possible so you can test all
these things how it works in the
practice okay let's look briefly main
features make an overview uh before I
show you few print screens I want to
show you how you can enable this
functionality when you start with
feature management this is only one way
process so once you start you have first
to choose data transfer and data
transfer will uh offer you two options
first is if you're already user you are
using busy Central you can choose
transfer existing 1089 data from your
base app and if you choose you need to
choose which year is your active year
and system will just use everything what
you had earlier and transfer to IRS
reporting periods and codes so you will
have uh brand new data in new app copied
from existing this is not one to one
because this is I said different design
but it
works second option is you do not want
to use your existing data you want to
create for a new setup so you can choose
default data and we are providing
default data for the for the next year
so you can create just default setup and
why and yes and again you will get all
this reporting Pags and CS everything
what is needed why this one is important
maybe you will use standard uh data
upgrade transfer from existing data in a
most situation but when you have new
customers when you enable new customers
you cannot transfer from existing data
so in this case for any uh of new
companies new customers you will use
this create with new setup so they will
get all fresh new and correct data for
working
what we have in 1089 forms and four
boxes first you will see we have this
IRS reporting periods as I mentioned we
have starting and ending dat so we can
have uh more um uh different periods in
the same time you need to use you need
to mention what is active period but you
can have different periods for reporting
then you can use different types of
supported forms for each of the on 1089
forms then you have 1089 form boxes
where you can specify um the different
uh situations minimum reportable amounts
everything what is related with amounts
next you need to configure vendors this
time it will be not direct to vendor
card you have IRS setup for vendor so
when you run IRS setup uh you can change
U your default codes you can use
different um uh uh 1089 1089 codes and
um in different periods uh uh vendor can
be eligible for different 1089 codes
okay on one can be default but you can
you will have much more space much more
options using this setup and then 1099
document you can see example of this
document now as I said we have header we
have lines uh this exists as a document
what is important to remember one form
for is one document and you have more
form boxes and it means one more for
example you have miscellanous and yes
for this form it can be only one you
cannot have for example neck and
miscellanous in the same document
because uh they different uh form types
for printing but one document is for one
form but you can have more different
form boxes as form boxes can him
different uh uh amounts reportable
amounts and so on so this is important
to find um you can find all uh details
included in these calculated amounts
after we explain how you can configure
to to have it or to not have but this is
on you how you will make a setup and yes
you can handle with different status
when you create you will see status is
open then you can continue with
different statuses some of statuses will
come automatically some of them will be
manually made and when you finish with
this you need to print and
send just to remind you once again you
will not print original preprinted form
by IRS so you will not order uh from IRS
uh original forms anymore now um you
will deliver to IRS through uh
integration with Iris apis in as I said
in next few minors and for vendors you
can print copy B and two uh C is for you
uh but again on a plain paper as a
substitutions with all details we have
original even all these instructions you
have there you will see after we show
how to configure instruction so
everything is there everything what we
have original form this is just design
is a bit different but everything what
exists in original form it will be
printed there so after that you can send
via email or physical
mail uh you can uh configure IRS and
respons a person for emailing this is
important we can use standard vendor
email but if you have for example
commercial email for this vendor and you
want to send um on different email now
you can enable different email so you
can have IRS responsible person for
email so you can send directly to this
person it will be much easier to have
additional option for sending and we
have t number and this this is really
important
because um you should you should secure
this te number especially when we
sending VI maale even uh male physical
mail but especially Emil now what we can
uh what we can do we can make a
setup Yeah by default you can print
original tetin uh your company te and
your vendor team that's okay but you can
use a setup to hide this is allow by the
low only four last digits to be showed
you can uh you can choose to make this
setup only for your vendors or for your
company vendors alog together so you can
secure this T number and you can easily
use emailing for this uh dis spender
without any security
issue um yes you have this 10894
statements setup so all these form boxes
you can set up by you and you have IRS
form instruction setup so you can easily
in make instructions and for emailing
you will see you can you will get some
default uh
email how how you can send but you can
change by
yourself I I I will keep this for AR to
show now when he starts so now I think I
finish with all my slides and I will
give uh display and Stage my colleague
Arthur to show you full endtoend demo
Arthur um as Alexander mentioned the
feature is available uh in the feature
management uh so unless you enable the
feature uh you still going to use the
old 1099 base
application and after you enable the
feature in the feature Management in one
company uh it is basically enabled for
all the companies so the other way of um
setting up the feature will be opening
the assisted
setup and from the assisted setup you
can find the setup and IRS forms
feature and when you click this one you
can see the guide page uh on the first
step we explain uh what is all about
what you want to get on the next one uh
there are exactly a few options
Alexander management so first of all
create new setup this is for the fresh
installation if you're a new customer
and the second one will be transfer
existing data if you already have some
data in the old 1099 base application
feature and you want to transfer this
data to the new IRS forms app uh and of
course we want to do this perer
reporting here um let me specify
reporting here I want to use create new
setup option and go next the next step
will be a few options for the IRS forms
apps the first one is called collect
details for line uh this is important if
you want to see some kind of the details
uh of the form document line I will show
you when the form document is ready uh
what this option means and the next
options it's called protect T and this
is exactly to make
uh tax indication number on the printing
forms more secure uh by default the
option is none but you can always select
protect TNN for vendors or for vendors
and the company and let's choose exactly
this
option and that will be the last step uh
so the IR forms is completed at that
point now let's open the page uh that is
called IRS reporting
periods and here we can uh see the IRS
reporting period and from here we can
open all the necessary setups forms
vendor setups adjustments and the
documents and let's start one by one uh
when I click forms uh I can see all the
usual forms uh like you had previously
in 1099 Bas application but right now it
is important that all these forms are
connected to the IRS reporting
period uh and then from the uh for I can
open the form boxes and you can see the
usual list of all the form boxes with
the minimum reportable amount uh as you
can see all the data is generated
automatically from the guide page let me
go
back uh also you can notice two actions
here the first one is called edit
statement and this is the uh exactly the
flexible setup Alexander management for
printing form so here you can specify
the setup of how you want your printing
forms to work uh you can specify the
print value type filter expression Rog
totaling so this is really flexible and
in case you want to print uh your form
differently uh the next one is called
edit instructions and this is also the
part for the um printing form here you
can uh set up all the printing
instructions uh for header for every
single box and I will show you where
exactly you have these instructions uh
on the printing
form um let me go back uh the next will
be let me skip the vendor setup I will
go to the adjustments uh this is also
the usual feature but here you can do
this for the reporting here uh let me
choose the
vendor and let me choose the four
missios and Miss 01 and the amount 100
so I'm setting up the adjustment for
this vendor for this code and what is
important for this reporting
here let me go back and then let me show
you how you can create the new reporting
periods so let's say you want to set up
the new reporting period And I guess
you're curious how you want to get all
the forms and vendors and adjustments of
course you don't need to create all
those manually for this you have the
special action that is called copy setup
prom uh so once you created the period
you click copy set set up
from and here you need to specify the
from period when we open the list we can
see all the periods except of course
this one uh we can select
2026 and then click okay and then we can
see some details so what exactly being
copied we can see that four forms 47
form boxes vendor boxer adjustments and
form statement Lines been copied and of
course we can check this we can click
forms and we can see absolute the same
forms copied from the other
period um now let me continue with the
2026 and open the important part of the
setup that is called vendor setup and
once again this is setup per reporting
period I'm going to choose the vendor
right here and I'm going to choose the
code and the um form box um what is
important that we added here and we you
didn't have in the previous version of
the feature you don't need to add all
the vendors here manually as you can
imagine you can have thousands of
vendors and you need to type all of that
manually one by one you don't need to do
this and let me show you how you can
make your life a little bit easier there
is an action that is called Suggest and
when you click this you can specify the
filters for the vendors to add those
vendors to the vendor form box setup and
I have already made a setup for a few
vendors let me choose the partner type
person and then I only want to consider
uh domestic vendors uh domestic and when
I click okay uh I can see that are few
vendors added to my form so you don't
need to add them
manually and of course yeah let me
continue
the specification of the form uh number
on the form box number
the other important part uh of this
vendor form box setup uh is in the
action that is called propagate so
imagine that you already posted some
invoices and payments for a certain
vendor but you didn't have a setup for
example you just forgot to assign uh a
specific IRS code to this vendor but you
already have the entries so now what you
want to do you want to have you want to
take this form and form boxes and you
want to propagate these changes to
existing vendor Ledger and
you don't want to open vendor Ledger
entries and you don't want to go one by
one to each invoice and specify okay
this invoice miscellanous one this
invoice missell one as well you want to
do this automatically and for this you
have the action that is called
propagate uh so you choose your vendor
setup uh the dates will be taken from
the reporting period and here you can uh
select what exactly you want to consider
do you want to consider purchase
documents or or you want to consider
vendor Ledger entries which are already
posted entries or you want to consider
both so once you do this and once you
click okay those documents and those
entries uh will be filled in with the
form uh miscellaneous
01 that is it with the vendor form box
setup uh let me show you how does it
work in the vendor card so when I go to
the vendor card and and that is the
important to show you uh the fields that
been added in scope of this IRS forms
app first of all you can
see uh the miscellanous code here in the
vendor card of course you don't need to
set up in the vendor card this is only
the non-editable fields and you can
click here and you will be look up to
the vendor form box setup from here so
this is just for the visibility the
usual way of showing you what is the
code is assigned to the vendor then
right below you can see two fields that
is important for the emailing Story the
first one this called receiving 1099
eform consent so this one should be
enabled if you want to send emails with
IRS forms to your vendor so if it's not
enabled you won't be able to do this and
the next one is called email for IRS uh
so these emails will be used to send uh
PDF forms to to your
vendor now let
me create the purchase invoice for this
vendor and show you that the data is
taken from the vendor formbox
setup the bries invoice is created I'm
going to assign vendor invoice now and
below in the header you can notice that
okay we have the form number and form
box number on the those vales taken from
the setup and of of course you can
change them I can select any
miscellaneous forms I want for example I
can select 02 right here I can change
the default setup um you can also notice
that I have specified the payment method
uh code is called cash so in this case
it will be a little bit easier for me I
don't need to create payment uh manually
so once I create and post purchase
invoice I can get straight to the form
documents creation um let me finish with
the purchase
invoice I want to specify direct unit
cost more than minium reportable amount
and I want to post this purchase
invoice let me go back to the IRS
reporting uh periods and from here uh I
can open the documents and I want create
the form documents for this vendor and
for this docent when I click create
forms here we can have the period
prepopulated from the reporting period
and you can create the form documents
for all vendors and for all forms if
those two filters are blank or you can
choose specific vendor or you can choose
specific form so form documents will be
created only for those and the important
uh option is replace so once the form
document is created you can notice that
okay these numbers are not correct so I
want to probably change something in the
vendor Ledger entries probably I need to
change some I want to post additional
document and then I can use the option
replace to recreate the existing form
document let me click okay here and we
can notice that we have the form
document and I'm going to open this form
document so this is exactly what
Alexander mentioned so this is very
different from the previous experience
in the previous experience you posted
vend Ledger entries and then you just
print the report so you were not aware
about uh the values and the values where
they've been taken from uh right now you
have this information so you can notice
that you can look up to the calculated
amount in the line when I do this uh I
can see the 1099 form document line
details and this is the list of the
vendor Ledger entries connected to the
certain lines so this is exactly the
detalization that was missing in the
previous version of the feature of
course you have the amount here minimum
reportable amount uh you can have
adjustment amount and the important
field that is called including
1099 uh as you know uh 1099 works in the
way that if the amount is more than
minimum reportable amount then we need
to include this in the report but if
it's below the minimum report amount
then we not going to include this and in
the previous version of the feature uh
you are not quite sure okay do I have
the amount more than minimum or less
than minimum amount right now you can
see all the lines here but based on the
this field including 1099 you can
understand okay so I'm going to include
this code in 1099 report or I don't want
to include this in 1099 report so we all
have this information right now as
well now the next step will be the
submission of the 109 report we want to
send this electronically uh this is part
is not implemented yet and that will be
available in the one of the next
releases uh but we want you to test the
other features which is printing and
mailing and the important part is that
the form document needs to be in the
submitted State and for that we have
implemented the temporary solution with
the action that is called Market
submitted so you mark your form document
as submitted and you can notice that the
status right now is submitted and only
when the status is submitted you can
print your document and you can ml once
again so this part will be changed
instead of Markus submitted action in
the future releases you will have the
action that is called just submit and
the data will be sent electronically to
ARs and after that what you can do you
can print your form document uh you can
click
print and here you can choose the report
type copy B copy C and copy 2 those are
options uh Alexander
explained uh let me
preview this form and talk a little bit
more about this
one in the top of this printing form we
can have the type it's called copy B so
if you select copy CN or copy 2 you will
have the different uh label on the top
and then below you have the usual
section for the vendor information and
for the company information uh on the
left side you have all the details uh
name address basically everything um and
the important part is the tax
identification number you can notice
right here that those values are
protected so you only see the last four
digits below you can see uh the
miscellaneous code we have only
miscellaneous 02 and the
amount and on the very last page you can
see the instructions for recipients so
those are taken exactly from the
flexible setup that is called edit
instructions text so you can see them
right here if something is wrong you can
change them and the changes will be
reflected on this page let me go back
and show you the last part of my
presentation
emailing uh you can notice in the header
of the form doent that we have the
consent uh from the vendor for receiving
1099 forms electronically we have the
vendor email here and that means that we
can successfully email our PDFs um PDF
forms to this vendor when I click Send
email I can also choose two options copy
b or copy two so these are only options
which make sense for the vendor let me
choose copy B uh I want to click
okay and I want to send you can notice
that uh now we have the options copy B
send change to true so by this option
you can notice that okay I already
emailed this vendor with this PDF form
and I have already set up emailing uh
feature here I want to show you how that
would work on the vendor form box I have
the new email right here uh and here I
have the email subject that 1099 form
code copy for your records we have some
email body saying okay uh uh we want to
send you some 1099 forms and here I have
the attachment is PDF and I want to
download this and show you that this is
exactly the printing form I have
presented previously the important part
is that the
emailing uh subject an emailing body
this is not the hardcoded text this is
something that you can set up in the IRS
forms app and I will show you where
exactly you can set this up uh the page
is called IRS form setup you can open it
and here you can find the IML email
subject you can change this and the
email body and this one this is reach
control text so you can format this text
uh in the way uh you want this so this
is very flexible you can change this
text as
well and that concludes my presentation
back to you
Alexander wow um thank you Arthur for
great presentation and yeah uh let's
shortly wrap up new and modern user uh
experience new features uh configurable
reporting uh much more option better
security more transparency for users and
great automation so this is definitely
great functionality you will see yeah
you need to change uh how you're working
with n 9 reporting but this is much much
better much more options so you can
easily do uh many things you couldn't
earlier so AR to once more thank you for
a great presentation and I just wanted
to mention one one small thing before I
forget maybe you noticed during R2
presentation on a few uh setup page we
didn't had IRS 1089 form setup we had
IRS uh form setup and a few places it
was just IRS with without 1099 now I
just want to explain um we were thinking
uh maybe in the future we will introduce
more IRS uh things now this is not
promising do not understand me wrongly
we just wanted to predict maybe it will
be in the future so we do not want in
the future if we do this to create uh
second IRS and third IRS set up for
different purpose so you will find 1089
only on a fors what is exclusively for
1089 reporting but for all others we are
we kept only IRS setup or IRS form setup
something like that so we can reuse this
form eventually if we upgrade this
functionality with some other um uh
reporting or uh whatever is related with
IRS so this is not something what we are
what we are planning to do right now but
just to make good foundation so in a
future we can easily uh extend it if
needed uh before I close this session I
just want to remind you on a great BS
Center resources
first um join us on our Yammer Channel
AK msbc Yammer you can talk with you can
talk you can exchange messages with us
you can give us feedback you can very
often get some early test uh uh
environment there so we we are open
there full transparency we can talk
about all issues or all good things you
have so please join us then yeah we are
more the open to discuss publicly so no
problem Twitter or X or some other
channels uh you can see details here uh
but more official from Microsoft side
join us on our monthly BC office hours
there are many many different and
interesting topics and again you will be
uh you have opportunity to talk to ask
to discuss with us about some features
and if you have something is missing in
V Central in 1089 feature on some other
features never mind what about just
submitter idea AK msbc idea so we are
really listening all this idea and to be
honest this new functionality came
because came here because of your ideas
that means we couldn't deliver
immediately but maybe it was better
because we collected much more different
ideas and now I think we deliver a
really great amazing functionality and
if you forget all these you different
URLs please do not forget this one akbc
all because this is a place where you
can find not only this um information
this links but much more dozens and
dozens different links before I say
thank you uh I want to call you and to
enourage you to join us Q&A session it
will take approximately seven days after
BC lunch event six seven days I'm not
100% sure uh but you will be invited
definitely and what is important you
will have this time you will have enough
time to watch all this videos so you
will collect what is uh important what
we maybe missed in our presentation uh
some other ideas so you will have
collection all this information so when
you have Q&A you can ask you can ask
face to face through messages whatever
you prefer so please join us there and
we will be more than open transparent to
discuss both Arthur and I in this case
so thank you very much for watching this
session